socialmediainsanity.com 2017-12-14

# Privacy Policy | MyLeadSystemPRO

This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for the website that linked you here. We will notify you of changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new policy on this website. Review our Privacy Policy regularly so that you can stay informed of our current practices, as they may change in the future.

By using our services or submitting information, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Your assent to these practices is essential for us to provide our services. Similarly, we need you to provide accurate personal information so that you can be contacted and use our website and related services. You can opt-out and decide not to provide the requested personal information. However, by doing so, we will not be able to contact you and you will not be able to use our website and/or services.

The personal information we collect includes name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, user name, and password. Other personal information that you may submit is clearly labeled at the time you submit it. We use the information that we collect to provide our services, to contact you regarding our products and services, and to improve our site. We also share your name, address, telephone number, and other contact details with the member, if any, who referred you to our website. Once a third-party obtains your personal information, its subsequent use is controlled by their business practices, which is beyond our control. By providing us a telephone number and/or email address, you are expressly requesting that we and/or anyone to whom we subsequently share or transfer your personal information contact you at that number or email address. Note, however, that your payment information is used only for order processing purposes.

We automatically collect certain information from visitors to, and members of, the site, such as Internet addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring and exit page, operating system, timestamps, and clickstream data. We also track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers. This information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, and to administer our site so that we can constantly improve the quality of the services we provide.

We do not respond to your browser’s “do not track” signals or other mechanisms for indicating your preference regarding the collection personally identifiable information. Our site includes retargeting features, which enables us to show you ads after you leave our site. We use technology and services from third parties to accomplish this. These third parties use cookies (a text file stored on your device), pixels (a small piece of code included in our web pages), or both, to analyze your web browsing activity to help determine which ads to display to you when you are on other websites. No personally identifiable information is collected through these remarketing systems, though in some cases we do have the ability to tailor advertising based upon the portions of our site that have been visited.

When you pay for anything on our site using a credit or debit card—including your monthly membership fee—we collect the personal information needed to complete the transaction. This information includes your name, card number, and other necessary information, all of which is clearly labeled on the form you use to submit payment. We use an unaffiliated, credit card processing company to process your payment. We transfer your payment information—and you authorize us to do so—to this company solely for this purpose. The company does not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

Other than as described above, we do not permit third parties to collect personally identifiable information about your online activities when you use our website and related services.

Anything you send us, post on our site, or use with our service, such as emails or voice recordings, or if other users or third parties send us anything about your activities or postings, we will collect such information into a file specific to you. We use information in the file that we maintain for you, and other information that we obtain from your use of the services, to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, and enforce our membership agreements.

  We take measures to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of your information. We carefully limit access to the database in which your personal information is stored. Additionally, we share and/or transfer your personal information only in the ways set forth in this privacy policy.

We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability. We may also (and you authorize us to) disclose personal information about you to credit agencies, collection agencies, and/or merchant database agencies, as we deem necessary

This website is directed at adults, not to anyone under the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly distribute such information. We do not knowingly allow children under the age of 13 to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information through our website. Similarly, because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, we do not condition the participation of a child under 13 in activities on providing personally identifiable information. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from someone under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records. If we change our practices in the future, we will obtain prior, verifiable parental consent before collecting any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.

Contact us at the address below if you want us to change or delete any information that we have about you. We will respond to your request to access, update, or delete your information within ten (10) business days. Before we are able to provide you with any information, correct any inaccuracies, or delete any information, however, we may ask you to verify your identity.

  This website is owned and operated by:  
Upwards Enterprises, LLC  
500 East 4th Street #361  
Austin, Texas 78701

This privacy policy is effective as of June 2, 2015.
